Fox News obtained a photograph of the dispatch order
sent out after Border Patrol agents called in
that they were under attack.
The police department issued a statement yesterday
trying to walk the order back,
saying CPD officers did, in fact,
respond to that shooting scene
involving federal authorities on Saturday
to maintain public safety and traffic control.
However, two police sources told Fox News that's not true.
Two suspects were arrested for allegedly ramming their cars
into a CBP vehicle, and DHS says one suspect was flagged
in an intelligence bulletin last week
for threatening agents.
This weekend, she allegedly sideswiped an agent's car
and was carrying a gun.
That agent, unable to escape, shot and injured her.
Before we go further,
I wanna start with this first situation, Douglas.
We are in what we might call,
and some others have, an assassination culture.
And so when you put people in danger
and you cause a no-go zone
around going to help agents or law enforcement,
you're creating a perfect scene for someone to be killed.
Oh yeah, and it's been happening for years, this.
I mean, we've been talking in recent weeks,
understandably, about the assassination culture,
the culture of encouraging political violence
in this country.
I don't think that anyone has been more consistently
on the receiving end of threats of violence
than ICE agents in this country.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
In 2020, I was undercover with Antifa in Portland,
and I just saw the way they were behaving
towards the ICE agents.
They try to burn them alive in their buildings.
They set light to dumpster trucks
and wheel them into the doors in the hope they can't get out.
Now we have routinely the doxing of anyone who's ICE agents,
ICE agents having to cover their faces
for fear of retribution,
hit lists out online with bounties on the heads of agents.
I mean, this is obscene.
This should not be happening in this country.
These are federal employees.
Well, and not only the masking situation,
you've got the governor of California
saying, take the masks off.
So you've got them trying to protect themselves,
and the governor of a large state
that has a lot of illegal aliens
who are committing crimes in his state,
wanting to protect the criminals
over the people who've gone to take back order.
It's unfathomable, and I'm glad you bring up 2020
as they attempted to light that courthouse on fire in Portland.
The emergency motion that DOJ filed the Ninth Circuit
to reverse the order of the district court judge
there in Portland,
saying you can't deploy the National Guard.
And when you get to page six, listen to this.
They're still doing it, Douglas.
Protestors repeatedly tried to burn down
the Portland ICE office.
One protestor lit a flame, set fire to materials.
The mob then piled on additional tender
attempting to stoke the flames.
That's just one of several incidents
the government points to.
And then you have the situation that is,
I just can't even wrap my mind around.
Portland police not allowed to go into this bubble.
There's two liaison officers on either side,
and then they go into the bubble
to arrest Nick Sorter, conservative journalist,
for doing nothing according to him.
But don't go in to stop this kind of stuff.
This is why President Trump has to step in.
And just, I would say this,
you know, I spoke on Saturday,
Saturday in America with Tom Homan.
And I said to Tom, what's happening in Portland,
the stand down of the police that we're seeing,
is it happening in Chicago?
And this was right before this incident happened.
And he said to me, Chicago, New York, Portland,
it's not the rank and file police officers.
They want to do their job.
It is the Democratic lawmakers on top
creating this dangerous situation.
Well, and if you do eventually have to send in
law enforcement officers,
you've endangered everybody's life at that point.
Because now they're walking into something
that's already cooking with gas.
Well, absolutely, Harris.
And for those opposing what ICE is doing,
what's the alternative?
Just allow terrorists, cartel members,
child predators to remain in America?
I mean, is that what these mayors
and these governors are advocating for?
I mean, essentially it is.
And Douglas, I'm glad you mentioned the bounty story.
I was co-hosting Fox & Friends yesterday
when Secretary Nome broke that news.
She said some of our ICE agents and officers
have bounties put out for their heads,
2,000 to kidnap, 10,000 to kill.
Their pictures are being sent around networks.
And I asked her the follow-up question,
well, who's behind it?
You know, who is funding these bounties?
And she said cartels and terrorist organizations.
And she said they're working on a whole-of-government
approach along with the Treasury Department
to try to get to the bottom of who's funding these riots.
She said she was in Chicago just a couple of days ago.
They all have the same masks.
They all have the same signs.
And so inevitably, we know we have
a domestic terrorism problem because that's essentially
what is happening in these cities.
They're using violence to try to change
our government's approach, government policy.
But how much overlap is there with foreign terrorism?
And I think with some of these investigations,
hopefully we get to the bottom of that.
Yeah, I want to go back for just a second.
Illinois Governor JB Pritzker dismissed the danger
that agents are facing.
His state has filed a lawsuit against the Trump
administration for deploying the National Guard.
Let's watch.